还要个裹尸袋
Need another bag.
Mike 你在哪儿
Mike, where you at?
喂 这边儿
Yeah, over here.
毒品战
Drug war?
嗯哼
??
Barksdale刚回来 就对Marlo下手啦
Barksdale's coming back on my boy Marlo, huh?
靠
Shit.
来吧
Got it.
我不知道咱们在哪儿
Man, I don't know where we at.
咱们在巴尔的摩 Lamar
We are in Baltimore, Lamar.
马里兰州 巴尔的摩
Baltimore, Maryland.
这是那些王八蛋 这星期端掉的我的第二个窝点
That's the second crib of mine them motherfuckers cracked this week.
乱捅马蜂窝 保不齐谁挨蛰
Stir up a hornet's nest, no telling who gonna get stung.
都神经兮兮的
All paranoid and shit.
必须的啊
Gotta be.
他们干掉了Latroy
They got Latroy.
你们他妈的在街上干嘛
Hey, what the fuck is y'all on the streets for, man?
不知道在打仗吗
Don't y'all know there's a fucking war going on, man?
都给我死上车
Get the fuck in the truck, man.
纽约州车牌
那些塔楼哪儿去了
What happened to all them towers?
车轮滚滚
Slow train coming.
啥
huh?
是变革 Lamar 变革
Reform, Lamar. Reform.
火线重案组  第三季 第10集
the.wire.s03e10
* When you walk through the garden *
* you gotta watch your back *
* well I beg your pardon *
* walk the straight and narrow track *
* if you walk with Jesus *
* he's gonna save your soul *
* you gotta keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* he's got the fire and the fury *
* at his command *
* well you don't have to worry *
* if you hold on to Jesus hand *
* we'll all be safe from Satan *
* when the thunder rolls *
* just gotta help me keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* you gotta help me keep the devil *
就算是领袖危机吧 --Porp Joe
咱们该他妈的马上监听通话
We should be up on this shit, hearing voices.
假如我们能通过Bodie的电话 搞一个特征号码 就可以了
We get a signature number on Bodie's phone, we will be.
单靠那些一次性手机 我们就有足够的合法理由了
We got enough PC off the burners alone.
这些号码记录器每显示一个通话 都叫嚣着毒品交易
Every time these fucking pen registers click out a call...it screams drug conspiracy.
又不是我上法庭起诉案件
I'm not the one taking the case to court.
Pearlman需要与一名已知毒贩 搭上确切联系
Pearlman wants a specific link to a known drug trafficker.
这些毒品团伙  他们最快每一两周内丢弃手机
These drug crews, they're dumping phones every couple of weeks at best.
因此 等我们真能监听时 有效时间注定很有限
So when we do get a wire up, it's gonna be a limited run.
对手机运营商来说 丢弃手机
And dumping phones doesn't meet the cellular company's
不符合"紧急情况"的定义 对吧
definition of "exigent circumstance," right?
你的上司怎么打算
What's your boss willing to do?
Demper 他的注意力有点 过于放在明年的连任上了
Demper? He's a bit too focused on next year's re-election fight.
联邦调查局呢
How about the feds?
他们说 他们帮不了我们
They say they can't do anything for us.
你瞧瞧他们怎么用联邦通信法案的 他们真不含糊
And if you look at how they use the Federal Communications Act they're not lying.
对于国家安全事件 他们就用爱国者法案
For national security stuff, they use the Patriot Act.
一切都能通融
Everything else gets shorted.
事实是 通信业攥住了我们的卵蛋
The fact is, the industry has all of us by the balls.
原谅我的粗话 法官大人
Pardon my French, Your Honor.
好吧 我告诉你们 为了你们 我最多能这么做
All right, I'll tell you what. Best I can do for you is this.
你们给我准备一份 附带合法理由呈堂报告的书面证词样本
You give me a boilerplate affidavit with the PC from the court report.
然后 你们得到一次性手机的新号码 你就给我打电话
And then, as you get fresh numbers for the new disposables, you call me...
白天晚上 任何时刻 抓起电话
anytime, day or night, to jump phones.
那真是谢谢您
That helps.
可是即使他们已经丢弃了 我们还要继续追查他们的电话
But we're still gonna be getting up on their phones even as they're coming down.
是啊 有这可能
Yeah, probably so.
这真是太
This is so totally...
操蛋了
Fucked up.
【法语】我法语讲得很好
而你今天
很性感啊
Phelan法官很惦记你啊
Judge Phelan has you on his mind.
这都有多久了
How long has that been going on?
我估计 从我在他的法庭 第一次做有陪审团的审判开始
Started with my first jury trial in his court, I think.
我打赌 你的动议都赢了
I bet you won all your motions.
你要见我吗 长官
You wanted to see me, sir?
坐下
Have a seat.
我要感谢你表现出的忠心
I wanna thank you for the loyalty you showed...
移开那死尸
moving that body.
那不算最明智的  不过无论如何 我很感激
It wasn't the most sensible thing, but I appreciate it, nonetheless.
你是好样的 警官
You're a good man, Sergeant.
你有不错的直觉
You got good instincts...
就我看来 你是个不错的头目
and as far as I can tell, you're a decent supervisor.
可作为资深警官
But from where I sit...
在警务方面 你屁都不行
you ain't shit when it come to policing.
别往心里去
Don't take it personal.
不止是你 是我们所有的年轻警察
Ain't just you, it's all our young police...
你们一整代人
whole generation of y'all.
你想想看
No, you think about it.
你到这里一年多了 Carver
You've been here over a year now, Carver.
没人为你打掩护
You got nobody looking out for you,
没人愿意跟你交心
nobody willing to talk to you.
能这么总结吧
That about sum it up?
那可成问题了
Now, that's a problem.
我一直不觉得自己能理清楚头绪
And I didn't think there was any way I was ever gonna get my head around it...
可等到Dozerman为些屁事被枪击
but then Dozerman gets shot for some bullshit.
我就快忍无可忍了
And that's when I about reach my limit.
就在那时  我想到自由区Hamsterdam的主意
And that's when the idea of the free zone, of Hamsterdam, come to me...
因为毒品这事不是警务工作
because this drug thing, this ain't police work.
不 那不是
No, it ain't.
凭警徽和枪 我能派任何傻瓜去那些街角
I mean, I can send any fool with a badge and a gun up on them corners...
搜查贩子 没收小瓶
and jack a crew and grab vials.
可警务工作呢
But policing?
那可以称之为战斗
I mean, you call something a war...
马上 大家都会像武士一样奔走
and pretty soon everybody gonna be running around acting like warriors.
他们会当成讨伐战争一样干
They gonna be running around on a damn crusade...
扫荡街角 手铐横飞 尸横街头
storming corners, slapping on cuffs, racking up body counts.
你在打仗时 你需要一个敌人
And when you at war, you need a fucking enemy.
很快地
And pretty soon,
几乎每个街角所有人都成你的敌人了
damn near everybody on every corner is your fucking enemy.
很快 你本该执勤的社区
And soon the neighborhood that you're supposed to be policing...
那就成占据的地盘了
that's just occupied territory.
你听懂了吗
You follow this?
我想是的
I think so.
Carver 我想说的是
Look here, the point I'm making, Carver, is this.
打仗和执勤 它们不是一回事
Soldiering and policing, they ain't the same thing.
在我们继续走错方向以前
And before we went and took the wrong turn...
在开始这些战争游戏前
and started up with these war games...
警察要巡逻  他要了解自己的职责
the cop walked a beat, and he learned that post.
如果那区域发生事件
And if there were things that happened up on that post...
无论是强奸 抢劫 还是枪击
whether they be a rape or robbery or shooting...
他都应该得到那里人们的帮助 给他情报
he had people out there helping him, feeding him information.
可是每次我找到你
But every time I come to you,
我的情报警官 要消息
my DEU Sergeant... for information,
要弄清街上发生什么情况
to find out what's going on out there in them streets...
得到的都是些胡言乱语
all that came back was some bullshit.
你统计过 抓过人 也没收过赃物
You had your stats, you had your arrests, you had your seizures.
可是要你讲到保护社区
But don't none of that amount to shit... when you talking about
那些加起来也没用 对吧
protecting the neighborhood, now, do it?
你知道这所谓的毒品战争
You know the worst thing
最糟之处在于...
about this so-called drug war...
在我看来
to my mind...
它恰恰毁了警察的工作
it just... It ruined this job.
警长
Major.
- 有什么情况 - 来访
- What you got? - Incoming.
太阳报记者 他们去过自由区 三人都去过
A Sun paper reporter. Been to the free zones, all three of them.
到车上等我
Meet you at the car.
我在考虑 咱们可以重写书面证词
I was thinking, maybe we rewrite the affidavit...
添加一些我们从号码记录器获得的情况
add some of the stuff we're getting from the pen registers...
那样立案 提交给法官
build the case that way, take it to the judge.
你有法律学位吗
You have a law degree?
你如果有 那就让你来决定
If you did, it would be your call to make.
不是律师的 谁想假装律师啊
Who would pretend to be a lawyer that wasn't?
我就是说 我认为 咱们对这事过于谨慎了
I'm just saying, I think we're being too cautious on this.
我们要为Phelan多做一点儿准备
We're going the extra mile for Phelan.
现在的捷径  会给我们将来的听证会造成伤害
A shortcut now could cost us later in motions hearings.
这次窃听 咱们摊上Phelan了吗
We drew Phelan on this wiretap?
上一次 那个两面派就把我涮了
That two-faced hack sold me out, the last go-round.
放心 他没有竞选新任期 他会配合的
Relax, he's not running for a new term. He'll be fine.
是啊 他就是一烂人
Yeah, he's a piece of shit.
我们挡你路的时候  都是些烂人
We're all pieces of shit when we're in your way.
凡事要分情况
That goes with the territory.
明白了
Point taken.
那么 就是这些仓库 Winchester老房子
So it's these warehouses, the old Winchester Homes...
还有到Vincent街的无人街区吗
and the dead blocks down by Vincent Street?
所有三个区域
All three.
他们就是想让这里成为自由区吗
And they're just supposed to let it go on like this?
Colvin告诉我们  把街头交易赶到这些地区来
Colvin told us to push the street dealing in these areas...
然后我们会开始抓人
and then we would start locking people up.
可是到现在 没有一次逮捕
But so far, not a single fucking arrest.
市警局了解这情况吗
And they know about this downtown?
我觉得 他们对此一无所知
I don't think they have a fucking clue about it.
不过 你质问的时候 我想在现场
But I'd love to be there when you pop the question.
过来买啊
Come get redhead.
这真是...
This is just...
谁说不是呢
Tell me about it.
- 把这里收拾得挺好啊 - 是啊
- Got the place looking good. - Yeah.
现在要做的 就是去给你招些孩子
Now all that needs doing is to go out and get you some kids.
少来了 老兄
Come on, man.
你说得真轻巧
You making it sound easy...
不过 跟你说实话
but, tell you the truth...
我完全不了解 怎么应付这些跑腿的孩子
I ain't got no idea how to go at these hoppers.
我才不会因此睡不着
Oh, I wouldn't lose any sleep over that.
别人也不会
Nobody else does, neither.
咱们发现一个 号码吻合
We got one.
- 是他祖母 - 找我吗
- His grandmother. - Looking for me?
小子 我得告诉你多少次啊
Look, boy, there's no reason to leave your clothes in the washer.
别把衣服落在洗衣机里
How many damn times do I have to tell you?
奶奶 对不起 我就是忘了嘛
Dag, Mee-maw. I'm sorry. I just forgot, okay?
不过 我确实买了洗衣粉 我买了
But I did pick up the laundry soap. I picked it up.
洗衣粉 这肯定是个暗号
Laundry soap, that's definitely a code.
现在咱们听一个几年前
Now let's listen to an intercept we made of Bodie Broadus...
咱们在公共电话上截听的 Bodie Broadus的录音
when we were up on those payphones a couple of years back.
我都告诉你啦 我看到那小子 他说他没拿那玩意儿
Look, I'm telling y'all, I saw the boy. He saying he ain't got that thing.
相同的声音 没问题
Same voice, no question.
我去通知法官
I'll let the judge know.
在呈堂报告里参考这次声音比对
Reference the voice comparison in the court report.
咱们开工啦
We're up.
耶
Yeah.
我这里有货 呦 没错
Got it right here, yo. Yeah, that's right.
- Colvin警长 西部辖区 - Banisky 太阳报
- Major Colvin, Western District. - Banisky, Sun papers.
那么 这是你的主意
So, this your idea?
买一送一
Got one, get one.
咱们走一趟吧
Mind if we walk?
Apocalypse Apocalypse (毒贩产品名称)
Apocalypse. Apocalypse.
来份儿Apocalypse 这边 小个子
Got that Apocalypse. Right here, shorty.
你们让毒贩免罪销售
You got dealers selling with impunity...
毒瘾者当街吸食
addicts shooting up on the street...
人们来这里做公益 散发针头等等
people down here doing outreach, giving out needles and all.
总局里 谁知道这个情况啊
I mean, who knows about this down at headquarters?
瞧 领导很熟悉情况
Look, Command is well aware of the situation.
开始是有些顾虑的
While there was some initial concern...
可他们觉得我们可以破案子
But they feel that the cases we're gonna bring in...
- 案子 - 是啊 起诉 肯定的
- Cases? - Yeah, prosecutions, sure.
你的警官说 自由区内没人被逮捕
Your officers say no one's being locked up in the free zones.
瞧 我的警队只负责 把交易驱赶到指定地区
Look, my troops are only involved in pushing the trafficking to designated areas.
我是说 他们对调查方面完全不了解
I mean, they're completely ignorant of the investigative aspect.
那由城里刑警队负责
That's run out of CID downtown.
是吗 负责的探员是谁
Yeah? Who's the lead detective?
你瞧
Look.
我讲的已经越权了
I already said more than I should.
实情在于 你马上开始四处打听
The bottom line is, you start throwing calls around right now...
他们会感觉不妙 以为有人泄漏
they're gonna shit blue, thinking there's a leak.
他们就会提前结案 我们在这里辛勤的工作
They're gonna come up on the case early, and we won't get all we can...
就要付诸东流了
out of this good work we did down here.
你在告诉我 这都是一个执法战略吗
You're telling me all this is an enforcement strategy?
这能是别的什么吗
What the hell else could it be?
我是说 你以为 我们真的允许发生这种事吗
I mean, you think we would actually let this happen otherwise?
不是吧 Banisky
Come on, Banisky.
瞧瞧 瞧这烂摊子
I mean, look. Look at this mess.
有别的记者调查这个吗
Any other reporter gets on it...
报道权我给你 案子查完你再报道
I give it to you, and you run with it right then.
你放心
Absolutely.
一周时间  然后我必须有所报道 无论如何
A week. But then I gotta run something, no matter what.
Purple Haze  Purple Haze (毒品品牌)
Purple Haze, Purple Haze.
可以理解
It's understood.
这边来
?? Right there.
兄弟 啥风把你吹回来的
So, brother, what brought you back?
事不做完 让我心烦
It disturbs me to leave business unfinished.
听说 你在这里大展身手前 就被枪击了
Heard you was shot before you even got started down here.
你不像是那种被玩的人啊
Not like you to get played.
你是说 被出卖的人吧
Betrayed, you mean.
我在找他们派的那个人
I am looking for the man they sent.
听他口音 他是本地人 在街头长大
From his accent, he's homegrown, raised on the street.
很熟练 聪明 快30岁 黑人
Skilled, intelligent, late 20s, dark...
但脸上有道疤 像这样
but with a scar across his face, like so.
你跟这黑鬼有交往吗
You down with this nigga?
我知道他 没讲过话
I know him. Not to speak to...
不过 你要不知道那混蛋 你就无法插手这行当
but you can't be anywhere near the game and not know the motherfucker.
他跟Barksdale一伙儿
He with Barksdale?
他单干
He with himself.
有时 他跟一两个小伙子在一起
Except for when he running with a young boy or two.
距离初选有10个月 你现在要全力筹款
Ten months to the primary, and you right now should be all about money.
我明白 我明白 打电话筹款
I know, I know. Dialing for dollars.
你这周开始 马不停蹄 直到筹到你要的数字
You start this week, and you don't stop until you hit your numbers.
仅电视广告 我们就要筹到一百万美元
We're gonna need $1 million just for television.
你真的认为这能行吗
Do you really think this is doable?
机会不太大 不过 能行
The odds aren't great, but, yeah.
我觉得 这能行
I think it can be done...
只要众多会搞砸的事 不搞砸
as long as the thousand things that can go wrong, don't go wrong.
即使对一个白人吗
Even for a white guy?
即使对一个白人
Even for a white guy.
说到这点
Speaking of which...
我注意这里存在 显著的单一种族效应
I notice a certain monochromatic effect here.
咱们一定得要黑人面孔
One thing we're gonna need is black faces...
而且我们需要他们处于显要位置
and we're gonna need them in prominent positions.
你说对了
You're right.
咱们得开始考虑黑人领袖的支持
You gotta start thinking about endorsement by black leaders.
部门首长 社区领袖 当选官员
Ministers, community people, elected officials.
说到困难部分了
Here comes the hard part.
分流黑人投票 是让这种算计生效的唯一途径
Splitting the black vote is the only way to make the math work.
因此 Tony Gray必须加入竞选行列
So, Tony Gray's gotta get in the race.
他必须留在竞选中 他必须在竞选中保持活跃
He's gotta stay in the race, and he's gotta stay viable in the race.
此人有点不堪重任 不是吗
Guy's kind of a lightweight, ain't he?
归根结底 他是个好人
He's a good guy, all in all.
正好 他是个好人
Great. He's a good guy,
但是 咱们需要他吸走Royce的选票
but we need him to siphon votes from Royce.
我不清楚 跟Tony这回事...
I don't know. This thing with Tony...
这无关私交 Tommy 这是政治
It's not personal, Tommy. It's politics.
不容忍 就失败
Live with it, or lose.
喂 那个尖鼻子的小子 他要过去 你知道吗
Yo, yo. That boy with the sharp nose, he going, you know...
- 他要去Apollo - Apollo
- He going to the Apollo. - The Apollo?
对 他需要两张票
Yeah. He gonna need two tickets.
靠 Tweety Bird正在准备货
Damn. Tweety Bird working that shit.
王八蛋 我告诉你多少次 别用人名
Motherfucker, how many times I gotta tell you not to use no names?
哦 对 那我通知你啊
Oh, yeah, right. So I holler at you?
对 好吧
Yeah. All right.
- Apollo 像是剧院吗 - 像是125大街
- Apollo, like the theater? - Like 125th Street.
125克 8分之1公斤 两张票是说"乘以二"
125 grams, one-eighth of a kilo. Two tickets means "twice that."
- 目前唯一的新暗号Hamsterdam - Hamsterdam
- The only new code so far is Hamsterdam. - Hamsterdam?
我们认为 这可能跟毒品仓库有关
We're thinking it might have something to do with the stash house.
我去接Kima 跟进Tweety Bird的会面
Well, I'm gonna hook up with Kima, catch the Tweety Bird meet.
你对咱们的收获满意吗
You're happy with what we're getting?
再有一周这样的通话 我们就能搞清楚他们得联络网了
Another week of calls like this... and we'll have their network fleshed out
到时候就可以跟进更多的电话了
and plenty more phones to go up on.
我要跟警探们谈一会儿
I need a moment with the detectives.
行
Sure.
内务调查部接手Prez开枪的案子了 这是意料之中的
IID picked up Prez's shooting. It's to be expected.
光种族原因就够他们紧张应对了
The racial thing alone is tense enough that they gotta react.
这小伙太没运气了 是吧
No luck at all to that boy, huh?
给上级的报告
For the supervisor's report...
我需要问你们两人 是否发现任何迹象
I need to ask if either of you had any indication...
表明Prez有种族偏见
that Prez harbored racial prejudices.
他肯定有些怪毛病
Well, he harbored some weird shit, no doubt,
可我从未感到种族歧视
but I never got a racial vibe.
队长 你当真要问吗
Lieutenant, you seriously asking?
废话不提 可是如果Waggoner是白人 你认为他会挨枪子吗
Not to start no shit, but you think Waggoner gets shot if he's white?
警察通信代号 1黑人 2白人 3亚裔...
无线电描述 那是一号男性
Description called for a number one male.
我只是说说
I'm just saying.
上帝把星期天上午定为礼拜时间
The good Lord set Sunday morning aside for churchgoing.
即使Kenny Bird和Peanut
Even Kenny Bird and Peanut,
他们交火期间也遵重这休战协定
when they was warring had the good sense to respect the truce.
知道吗 Barksdale他们送来一顶帽子
You know them Barksdales sent a hat?
礼拜花冠
A church crown?
走上来 按门铃 把它放在门廊
Walked up, rang the bell, and set it down on the porch.
因为他们很惭愧
'Cause they ashamed.
Josephine女士恢复了吗
Is Miss Josephine mending?
她还有瘀伤 不过她没事
She bruised up still, but she all right, though.
可你还是不甘心
But you ain't.
除非我能一劳永逸解决问题
Not until I settle this for good.
嘿 Butch我要你去拿钱 再传出话去
Hey, yo, Butch, I want you to go inside my bank and spread the word.
Omar会给杀了他们的人的家伙现金奖励 你明白我意思吗
Omar paying cash money to get at them people, you feel me?
把你的钱留着吧
Hey, save your money.
- 拜托 Butchie 我一定得这样的 - 我是说 你不必付钱
- Come on now, Butchie, I got to do this, yo. - I'm saying you ain't got to pay.
Thomkins在McCulloh那边
Thomkins, up on McCulloh.
- 啥 那个殡仪馆里 - 嗯哼
- What, the funeral home? - mm-uhm.
你是说 你都看够了那些混蛋
You mean to tell me all this time you had a scope on them clowns...
你还一声不吭啊
and you ain't let loose a mumbling word.
我是想保护你啊
Caught myself looking out for you.
要紧的是 你要去对付那帮人
Fact of the matter is, your chances of going up against that mob...
全身而退的机会微乎其微
and coming back is as slim as a garter snake.
我现在忍不住啊 Butch
I can't help that now, Butch.
咋回事 我的人哪儿去了
What the fuck? Where's my people?
Slim Charles调走了他们 请来新的打手
Slim Charles pulled them. Hired new muscle.
Slim Charles 他啥时候..
Slim Charles? When the fuck did he...
数额怎么样
How's the count?
连续三周下滑
Down bad for the third straight week.
我们再做缩头乌龟  就会坚持不了多久的 String
And the shelf-life of the shit we got, it ain't gonna last, String.
我知道 Slim告诉他们 贴身保护你
I know. Slim said they're to stick to you for protection.
传这里 传这里 投得漂亮
Give it here. Give it here. Nice shot.
传出来 传出来
Dribble it back out. Dribble it back out.
- 你要运球 - 笨蛋
- Get your dribble on. - Fucking hack.
喂 别着急
Yo, yo, easy, easy.
你们乱动手
Y'all just hacking my man up.
犯规机器
Foul machine.
运得漂亮
Nice drive.
他们有点不守规矩 对吧
Kind of unschooled, ain't they?
你那屁孩挑三拣四啊
What the fuck you cherry-picking for?
我的任务是观察 那就是说只管呆在路边 不管不顾
That observation meant as just a casual curbside, "Fuck you"...
或者你打算站出来帮帮他们
or are you looking to step up, maybe help out here?
我想试试看
I'm gonna give it a try.
我在找一些对拳击感兴趣的孩子
I'm looking to get some kids interested in boxing.
拳击
Boxing?
瞧这边
Look here.
这是我的暂停区
This is my time-out corner.
我把不能一起玩的孩子派到这儿
Where I send children who can't play nice together.
注意了 这人要开办一个拳击课程
Listen up. This man's starting a boxing program.
从你们这些人的德行看 报报名可能是好事
And from the looks of some of y'all, signing on might be a good thing.
你肯定需要
You gonna need it.
他拳头的唯一用处  就是握住他的鸡鸡
The only thing he know how to do with his fist is wrap it around his cock.
去你妈的 想找揍啊
Fuck you, man! Gonna kick your ass!
来啊 混蛋 你屁都不算
Come on, motherfucker, you ain't shit.
放手 坐下 坐下
Ease up. Sit down, sit down. Sit down.  Come on, man. Sit down, man. Sit down.
别 伙计
No, man.
老弟 你右侧空虚
My man, you dropping your right.
你看 要是那小子训练过 他就海扁你啦
See, if young'un there was trained, he'd whip you.
瞧他那副挨揍的德行
Look like he the one that got beat.
站起来 我给你示范一下
Stand up, let me show you something.
来吧 伙计 我不会伤害到你的
Come on, man. I ain't gonna hurt you.
Yellow tops  yellow tops Yellow tops
Yellow tops, yellow tops, got them yellow tops. Yellow tops.
瞧见没
See that?
好啦 坐下
All right, sit down.
瞧 你们要想多学点儿
Look, if y'all wanna learn more...
在Gilmor那个老轮胎厂 我有个拳击场
I got a gym down on Gilmor in the old tire plant.
欢迎你们来 好吧
Y'all are all welcome. All right?
我看见Tweety Bird车停那边
I saw Tweety Bird parked up there.
咱们要做的就是等他再出现
All we gotta do is wait for the re-up.
我希望这些浑球别到处惹事 害咱们白等一整天
I hope these fucks don't dick around and make us sit here all day.
怎么 这烦到你了
What, this is eating at you?
没 我很好
No, I'm good.
对哦 我都看出来了
Yeah, I can see that.
记得我跟你讲过的那个女人吗
Remember that woman I was talking about?
那女政客吗 进展如何
Politician woman? How's it going?
那不成 搞砸了
It ain't. Turned to shit.
觉得我不属于任何有意义的世界
Feel like I don't even belong to anyworld that even fucking matters.
因为你是警察吗
'Cause you're a cop?
不 不只是这个
Nah, it's not just that.
有次我约会她 她在酒店房间里 顶层的
It's like, I went to meet her once. Shewas in a hotel room, the top floor.
我按了电梯按钮 它压根不到那层
I punched the button on the elevator. It doesn't even go there,
因为你要到那特定楼层 你就必须有某种特别钥匙
'cause you haveto have some fucking special keyto even get to that special fucking floor.
于是我到前台  某个臭屁的混蛋通知楼上
So I go to the front desk, some sneering fuck calls upstairs...
给我跟人上床的许可
to give me permission to go get laid.
我听她谈论的话题
I listen to the shit she talks about...
有生第一次 我觉得像个门童
first time in my life, I feel like a fucking doormat.
好像任何有点儿头脑的人 该让他的人生有所作为 明白吗
Like anyone with any smarts would do something else with his life, you know?
赚大钱 或者当选
Earn money or get elected.
好像我只是个为我鸡鸡而喘气儿的机器
Like I'm just a breathing machine for my fucking dick.
我说真的
I'm serious.
在三个警区里 我都是最聪明的货
I'm the smartest asshole in three districts...
她看我的眼神 仿佛我是个傻逼
and she looks at me like I'm some stupid fuck...
在玩那些几分钱赌注的游戏
playing some stupid game for stupid penny-ante stakes.
她看透我了 Kima
She fucking looks through me, Kima.
你 呆在车里
Yo, stay in the car, man.
高个子说紧跟着你
Tall man said to stick to you like...
我踩你脑袋的时候 高个子会在吗
Tall man gonna be there when I stomp on your fucking head?
呆在车里
Stay in the car.
喂 快点儿讲 我还要去开会
Yo, make it short, man, I got a meet to make.
去他妈的会
Oh, fuck the meet!
你比我那肥老婆的逼都难找 黑鬼
You harder to get at than my fat wife's cunt, nigga.
你们全知全能的Barksdale 能负担停手 装孙子
Yeah, you high-and-mighty Barksdalescan afford to sit back and play low-key.
可我们有人还得拼命过生活
But some of us gotta work for a goddamn living.
啥 你们以为 这烂摊子没搅乱我们的生意吗
What, you think this mess ain't fucking up our business?
这代表Avon愿意跟Marlo坐下和谈 解决这问题吗
That means Avon's willing to sit downand talk with Marlo, work this shit out?
如果那不可能 String 我就告诉你个坏消息
Well, if that don't happen, String, I got you some bad news.
我和伙计们一起开了个会
Me and the boys had us a sit-down.
达到有效人数 搞了一次投票
Got a quorum and took a vote that says...
如果你们不结束这次战争 我们决定把你们排挤出去
if y'all don't quit this war, we have a mind to shut you out.
我说出去的时候 String 我是指断货
And when I say out, String, I mean out the package.
伙计们认为 如果不能制止你们
The boys don't wanna extend the good shit...
抢地盘 打仗 就不再给你们优质货
if it's gonna keep you and your peoplesout on them corners, banging.
那小子呢 他他妈的怎么说
What about the boy? What the fuck he say?
Vinson说 如果Marlo能保留他的地盘  他愿意和谈
Vinson say Marlo willing to talk if he can keep his corners.
现在听我说 String 不是我们忘恩负义
Now hear me on this, String, we ain't no ingrates.
我们都认同你对合作社的贡献
We all recognize your contribute to the co-op.
可情况是这样的
But the feeling is this.
如果你都管不住你自己的人手的时候 你就不适合当头领了
It ain't right for you to be at the head ofour table when you can't call off your dog.
就算是领袖危机吧
Call it a crisis of leadership.
你要告诉他们吗
You're gonna tell them?
肯定要
Got to.
有健康义工 报社记者和我恼火的警队夹击
Between the health-care workers, there porter,and my own pissed-off troops...
这肯定会曝光
it's gonna come out.
不是明天 就是后天
Either tomorrow or the next day.
咱们该拘捕一些人 把这做成策略性的
We should make a few arrests, make it look tactical.
不成
Nah.
如果我们开始在Hamsterdam抓人 你知道有什么结果吗
You know what happens if we startlocking people up in Hamsterdam?
整个辖区其余地区变回原先的粪坑
The whole rest of the district goes back to being a shithole.
不行
Nah.
如果Rawls拿我问罪
If Rawls is gonna hand me my ass...
至少先让我有机会讲明我的理由
at least give me a chance
Devonne
Devonne.
那咋回事
What was that?
必须干掉她
It needed doing.
有人中枪了
Somebody just got shot!
我得交出给Denali通风报信的奸细
What you want I should give the snitch that clued us to the Denali.
我们没搞到Marlo 不过还是得这样
I mean, we didn't get Marlo, but still...
不 他那部分还是归他 做得要彻底
No, he kept his end up. Go it all.
Avon 我要讲事情
Avon, I need a word, man.
等我通知你 让他们都出去
Let me holler at you. Get them niggas out of here, man.
瞧这个 String
Check it out, String.
这玩意杀伤范围 大概50米
This shit got the kill range of, like, 50 meters.
Slim从某些士兵那儿搞来的
Slim got this from some soldier coming back from wherever.
我跟Prop Joe他们谈过了
You know, I spoke to Prop Joe's people.
- 他们认为我们能解决好 - 和谈
- They think we can work this out. - A sit-down?
现在时机刚好 伙计
It's the perfect time for it, man. I mean...
你的确重树声望 你名声之外了
you done represented yourself, man. Your name ringing out...
现在你着实让Marlo吃了一两次苦头
now that you done taken Marlo down a notch or two, man.
何不趁咱们领先时收手呢
So why not quit while we's ahead?
先让我把这件事摆平 伙计
Just let me get this thing right, man.
然后 我们再更往常一样去谈
Then, you know, we get back to business as usual.
他们要把咱们甩了 Avon
They gonna cut us out, Avon!
Prop Joe和那些人 他们做了一次投票
Prop Joe and them niggas, man, they took a vote.
他们要把咱们甩了
They gonna cut us out.
要是真这样 咱们肯定就没货了 所以即使咱们赢了 最后还是会输掉
We ain't gonna have that dope, so even if we win, we lose...
因为咱们不会有货卖到那些地盘
'cause we ain't gonna have no product to put on them fucking corners, B.
Avon 瞧你啊
Avon, look at you.
现在不用针头就吸毒啊 伙计
Fucking shooting dope without a fucking needle right now, man...
大权在握时吸毒 作走卒的角色
getting high on a power trip, playing fucking soldier.
你得消停一下 考虑咱们的生意
Yo, you gotta sit back, man, and think about our business.
你他妈要干嘛
What the fuck you want?
那个王八蛋 他真行
That motherfucker. He good.
怎么了
What happened?
你瞧 Avon 你得想想 咱们做这行是为了什么 伙计
You know, Avon, you gotta think about what we got in this game for, man.
是为名声吗
Was it the rep?
是为了咱们的名字声震 那些操蛋的犹太区吗
Was it so our names could ring out on some fucking ghetto street corners, man?
不 伙计 是为了超越这行的事业
Nah, man, there's games beyond the fucking game.
Avon 瞧瞧 你和我 咱们兄弟 B
Avon, look, you and me, we brothers, B.
我们以前没想到咱们能走到这么远
We didn't think we'll make it this fucking far,
可是如果咱们没站在这里
but fuck if we ain't standing here...
眼下 整个世界在咱们脚下
right now, with the whole world at our feet.
整个世界 伙计  不是那些操蛋的街角
The whole world, man, not these fucking corners.
整个世界 B
The whole world, B.
你知道Slim刚告诉我什么吗
You know what Slim just told me?
Devonne刚死了
Devonne come up dead.
她被枪杀的 嘴里一枪 乳房上各一枪
She was shot, one in the mouth, one in each tit.
你还想谈休战吗 String
You still wanna talk truce, String?
你说我需要多长点教训 你是对的
You right when you say I need to learn more discipline.
可这个
But this?
你有更好的办法
You could do this better.
你是理想的诱饵 Lamar
You're the perfect bait, Lamar
他们能看出你的矛盾心态
They'll see you as conflicted.
你的恐同心态发自肺腑
Your homophobia is so visceral.
你瞧瞧
You see that?
我还没进那地方
I ain't even stepped inside the joint yet,
你就说我是舔鸡鸡的了
and you calling me a cocksucker already.
你来对地方了吗
You in the right place?
我在找个叫Omar的人
I'm looking for someone named Omar.
没姓 脸上有这样一道疤
No last name. Scar across his face and shit.
叫Omar的刀疤脸吗 听着特别 可我帮不了你 你喝酒吗
Scarface named Omar? Sounds different but I can't help you.You drinking?
你再等四年好了啊
Maybe you wait four years.
不 必须是现在
No. It has to be now.
必须是三人竞选 Tony这次要参加
It's gotta be a three-way, and Tony's gonna go this time.
我就是...
I'm just...
Tony是我在议会最久的朋友
Tony's my oldest friend on the Council.
那你不能先去跟他谈谈吗
Well, couldn't you go talk to him first?
把事情挑明
Put it on the table?
说 "让最好的人当选"
You know, "May the best man win"?
事实在于
Truth is...
单挑Royce 他也赢不了
he can't win alone against Royce, either.
他有自有话语权 别的就没有了
He's got the bumper stickers, but not much else.
想用教育议题竞选
Wants to run on education.
我是说
I mean...
凭这个你能走多远
where do you go with that?
如果我跟Tony说实话 他退出了 我就无法当选
If I level with Tony and he gets out, then I can't win.
我需要他参加竞选
I need him in the race.
我感觉糟透了
I feel like shit.
真的
I really do.
看着不怎么样嘛
Don't look like much.
- 这不是很烂 - 对 就是
- This don't look like shit. - Hell, yeah.
- 就这么松松的玩意儿 - 对 就是
- This some weak-ass shit right here. - Hell, yeah.
各位 我们有衣柜 有装备
Man, we got lockers, got gear.
- 这都磨破啦 - 来吧
- It's all peeling and shit. - Go long.
嘿 嘿 传这边儿
Hey, hey, hey, pass it here.
- 你把我弄得脏兮兮 - 去你的牛仔裤
- You getting me all dirty and shit. - Hey, fuck your jeans.
去你的 贱人
Fuck you.Bitch.
我们确认了Tweety Bird的会面 盯了他一晚上
We clocked the meet with Tweety Bird, stayed on him overnight...
跟踪他到一处可能的仓库 然后跟着回到Woodlawn的老窝
tracked him to a possible stash house...  and then home to nest in Woodlawn.
拍了照片 他的标志
Got photos, his tags...
- 出什么事了 - 他们把那些手机扔掉了
- What happened? - They ditched their phones.
号码记录和监听功能 在3点钟都失效了
The DNRs and the wire all died around 3:00.
我们监听手机仅有30个钟头
We were online just shy of 30 hours.
我以为 一次性手机 可以盯住他们几个星期的
I thought we had them on their burners for a couple of weeks.
不行了 最多有一周时间
Not anymore. It's a week at best.
我们刚花了9千块 换来18条监听记录
We just spent $9,000 and change for 18 intercepts...
其中5条是不相干的
five of them non-pertinent.
几乎每个毒品通话要花700块
That's close to $700 per drug call.
在弄清下一步方向以前 我们不该回去盯住Bernard和他女友吗
Until we see which way this goes shouldn't we get back on Bernard and his girl?
我是说 至少可以监听新的手机
I mean, get a line on the new phones at least.
可那样只能给咱们 刚用过的那30个小时
But that'll only give us what we just had, 30 hours.
有办法让我们抢占先机吗
Any way to get ourselves ahead of the curve?
如果有办法提前监听一次性手机
If there were some way to pre-wiretap the burners...
然后呢
And what then?
把它们成批放在Baba之类的店里 然后等着Bernard出现吗
Stick them on a rack at Baba-whateverand wait for Bernard to show up that day?
问题在于移动运营商
The problem is the wireless people.
他们声称 处理一份法庭指令 安排监听至少要4天时间
They claim it takes a minimum of four days to process a court order...
那还是我让地检署 以诉诸公众威胁他们之后
and that's only after I had my office threaten to go public on them.
敲敲键盘要4天时间 扯淡
Four days to hit a couple of keystrokes. Bullshit.
要是...
Well, what if...
不行
No way.
我知道你在想什么 我刚才想着同一桩事
I know what you're thinking. I just thought the same fucking thing.
好吧 注意 我告诉你的时候 把你的脚向左侧迈开
All right, look, man. When I tell you, put your left foot out, boy.
- 大叔在抚摸哥们的脚 - 是啊 他还在闻我的屁股
- Hey, Unc patting my man's feet. - Yeah, he smelling up my ass, too.
别再耍宝了
Stop with the damn clowning, man.
你们这么犯傻 怎么能学到东西
How the fuck you gonna learn something, acting like a damn fool?
你的脸被刺青 一点儿也不稀奇嘛
Yeah. Ain't no big mystery why your face got tattooed.
操 这人不能这么训你啊
Shit, that man can't talk to you like that.
我见过他揣着毒品 在那些地方出现
I seen his raggedy ass up at the spot, copping vials.
是啊 也许还卖他的屁股
Yeah, probably pimps his ass, too.
- 留神 王八蛋 - 耶 贱人 碰我啊
- Listen, motherfucker... - Yeah, bitch, touch me.
碰未成年人 等着瞧
Touch a juvenile, see what happen.
我们走吧 贱货王八蛋
Let's bounce. Bitch-ass motherfucker.
Lester
Lester.
我第一次见他抽烟啊
First time I seen him smoking.
恶习难改
Tough habit.
像贱人一样兜圈子
And pacing like a motherfuck, too.
当上领导责任重大
Heavy is the head that wears the crown.
Bay移动公司411热线 请问您在哪一州哪一城市
Bay Wireless Connect 411. What city and state?
马里兰州 巴尔的摩市
Baltimore, Maryland.
- 需要什么帮忙吗 - 接巴尔的摩警察局
- How may I help you? - Baltimore police.
- 哪个具体部门 - 西区分局
- Any particular department? - Western District police.
- 是紧急情况吗 - 不 不是紧急情况
- Is this an emergency? - No. Non-emergency.
伙计 他们给了你个下马威
Man, they did you with the bum rush.
那正是他们的伎俩
That's what they do.
他们靠挑起怒火对付内行
They past experts at plucking nerves.
你只需记住 他们基本无伤大雅
You just gotta remember they barely housebroke.
我告诉你吧 你都不会相信
I'm telling you, man, you wouldn't believe it.
他们有多么野 不服管教
They was all wild and shit  Wouldn't listen.
Andre 我要你缠住他
Andre, I want you to crowd him.
- 是 先生 我要缠住他 - 好的
- Yes, sir, I'll crowd him. - All right.
计时
Time!
你必须调整心态 坚持下去
You just gotta set your mind to stick with it.
那两个刚到这里是 要多野 有多野
When those two stumbled in here, they was wild as wild.
现在 他们每天到场
Now they come in every day.
"是 先生 不 先生"
"Yes, sir. No, sir."
依然相当粗野 不过 用正确的手段 他们就能做到
Still pretty rough but, you know, with the right breaks, they gonna make it.
怎么做
How?
他们愿意就努力 我不会让他们失望
Well, try as they might, I won't let them fail.
当你做到这个 就能控制他们的头脑
When you do that, it messes with their mind.
很快 他们就用尽他们的小伎俩了
Pretty soon, they run out of their little bag of tricks.
你怎么看那位
What do you think of that?
挺弱的
Pretty weak.
他可不弱
He ain't weak.
那就是突破点
That's the starting point.
不行 我想不起他的名字
Nah, nah, I can't put a name on him.
不过我见过他 他在西边活动
But I seen him around. He's off the West Side.
他不是毒贩子 除非他暗自操作
He ain't no drug dealer, unless he's doing it on the q.t.
你不能联络他 跟他玩玩吗
You can't go at him, game him?
我不清楚 Kima
I don't know, Kima.
我是说 那样很显眼
I mean, it'd be pressing.
她怎么样
What about her?
Lanvale那边的小Squeak
Little Squeak off of Lanvale.
认识 她以前给Turtle Wells的老帮派跑腿
Yeah, she used to boostfor Turtle Wells' old mob.
她也减了点儿体重 比我印象里好看不少
She's lost a little bit of weight, too. I mean,looking a lot better than I remember.
我记得那姑娘很多事情
And I remember a lot about that girl.
靠 Bubs 西边有你不认识的人吗
Damn, Bubs, is there anybody West Side you don't know?
只有正经市民吧
Just citizens and shit.
我的线人认识那姑娘
My CI knows the girl.
- 他能策反她吗 - 他很老练 当然
- He can work her? - He's smooth, yeah.
瞧这个
Check this.
那是西区分局
That's Western District.
- 什么 Stringer在给西区分局打电话 - 也许他要自首
- What, Stringer's calling the Western? - Maybe he's surrendering.
在咱们千辛万苦之后 我决不原谅这混蛋
After all the work we've done, I'd never forgive the son of a bitch.
下去 下去
Go down. Go down and out.
爽 瞧瞧这手
Oh, sweet! Look at the hands!
怎么了 我那些混混没露面吗
What's up? My knuckleheads didn't post?
不 他们去了 不过又离开了
Yeah, they did, but they left.
这边儿
Over here!
找打折货吗 老家伙
Looking for a discount, old man?
不 我来找你的
Nah, but I'm looking for you.
为啥 丢了东西吗
Why, something come up missing?
过来道歉的
Came past to apologize.
我当教练是新手 我们开始有点矛盾
I'm new at this coaching thing and got us off on the wrong foot.
我不会让你们觉得被放弃 不会记着你们的过错
I ain't gonna leave it between us, with you thinking I gave up on y'all.
王八蛋记性差得很 是我们抛弃了他的
Motherfucker's memory weak as shit. We the one bailed out on him.
无论如何 我现在来了
Anyway, I'm here now.
让我弄明白
Let me understand.
你们要把一批手机卖给毒贩子
You wanna sell drug traffickers a series of cell phones...
手机都预先获得监听许可
that are pre-approved for telephonic intercepts.
而你们要我签署监听的法庭指令
And you want me to sign off on court-ordered taps...
在我对这批手机签署法庭指令的时候
on a bunch of phones that, at the time I'm signing the order...
它们尚未被用于任何非法活动
have not been used for any illegal activity whatsoever.
你要寻求先例的话 法官大人 几乎没有
If you're looking for precedents, Your Honor, there aren't any.
这最多是依据情况而定的合法理由
It's circumstantial PC at best.
管它的 咱们就试试
What the hell, let's do it.
让法庭上诉解决它吧 除非本案能走到那步
Let the Court of Appeals sort it out, if it even gets that far.
好强的司法意识啊
Quite the legal mind.
请你喝一杯吧
Buy you a drink?
你他妈的怎么从我身后靠上来
Why the fuck you coming up behind me?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
乱头发 (Jimmy外号)
Bushy top.
被传来的 我没想到 这么晚能在这儿找到你
He called. I didn't know if I'd find you here so late.
为明天的情况通报做准备
Just getting ready for COMSTAT tomorrow.
有啥情况 局长
So what's up, Major?
你们组还在调查毒品战争 对吧
So your unit is still working a drug war, right?
查得很辛苦
Working it hard.
有个人Avon Barksdale 跟你们有什么关系吗
Does the name Avon Barksdale do anything for you?
- 他是个参与者 - 他是主要目标
- He's a player? - He's the main guy.
我们以为他完蛋了 可他在九月突然出现
We thought he was down, but he popped up in September.
你把他算进去 说明暴力情况就要很长时间
You add him to the equation, it goes a long way to explaining the violence.
那么 如果他中枪  这就能够解释吧
So it wouldn't be a stretch if he got shot?
你听说 他被枪击吗
You heard he got shot?
你知道时间地点吗 我可以很快查清楚
You know when or where? I could run it out quick.
别 那样没什么用
Nah, ain't gonna make no difference.
他又不会出现在急诊室 据我所知啊
He didn't post up at any emergency room... from what I hear.
局长 我坦白跟你讲 我们正在监听他的人马
Major, I'm gonna be straight with you. We're running wires into his people.
几乎只在街头人马的程度 目前 我们没监视到他本人
barely above the street. So far, we haven't even put an eyeball on him.
假设他本人就在那里
Supposed to be laying his head there.
我需要你查实这个 尽快答复我
I need you to check that out, get back to me as soon as you can.
你有个线人
You got a CI, huh?
你想看看你的(男)人信用是否可靠
You wanna see if your man's creds are bona fide.
别想套我 乱头发
Don't try to play me, bushy top.
我没说男人 我没说女人
I didn't say male. I didn't say female.
好吧 我马上安排监视
All right. I'll get surveillance going right away.
根据我的线人  Barksdale的名字在那房产登记上
According to my source, Barksdale's name is on the paperwork.
真的
No shit.
现在 你给我确认一下 来电打到我的手机
Now, you get me a confirmation on that and call me back on the cell.
- 明天走运啊 - 是啊 对啊
- Good luck tomorrow. - Yeah, right.
联邦街区项目批准 给西区建设加油
9家本市开发商获得奖励基金
Sham
Sham.
Shamrock
Shamrock.
替我把这个送给Levy
Run these over to Levy for me.
告诉他 我让他看看这个
Tell him I want a read on it.
看看
A read?
新开拓下眼界 告诉他 我明天给他打电话
Fresh eyes. Tell him I'll call him tomorrow.
好吧
All right.
走吧 保镖先生
Come on, Mr. Bodyguard.
那么 我们打算这样接近她
And so we're gonna come at her like that.
你们要我把这些手机卖掉吗
So you're gonna give me these phones to sell?
钱要收回来 Bubs
The money comes back, Bubs.
全部收回吗
All of it?
- 那是Beadie Russell吗 - 看着像是
- Is that Beadie Russell? - Looks like.
喔 你们不能从这条车道拐弯啊
Whoa, yo, you can't turn from this lane!
亲爱的Beatrice Russell
Sweet Beatrice Russell.
我只想打个招呼
I was just gonna say hey.
North和Pulaski街口
North and Pulaski.
照片是下午4点拍摄的 这时是街头交易的黄金时段
That photo was taken at 4:00 p.m., prime time for the street-level dealer.
这是在Riggs和Calhoun街口
That is Riggs and Calhoun.
Mount和Fayette街口
Mount and Fayette.
Edmondson和Brice街口 这是你原来的巡逻区 副局长
Edmondson and Brice. That's your old foot post, Deputy.
我知道那地方 局长
I know where it is, Major.
我所不知道 特别想知道的是
What I don't know and very much want to know is...
巴尔的摩西区的毒品交易在哪里
where is the West Baltimore drug trade?
局长 我希望你给我们看的 这些照片不是摆拍的
I hope, Major, these are not staged photographs you're showing us.
不 长官 它们不是的
No, sir, they are not.
不 副局长 我另辟蹊径
No, Deputy, I found another approach.
我洗耳恭听 Bunny
I'm all ears, Bunny.
- 我把他们从街角清除了 - 我靠
- I moved them off the corners. - God damn it!
别给我卖关子 局长 我能看出了
Don't be coy with me, Major. I can see that.
我想知道的是  你他妈的怎么把他们清除掉
What I want to know is how the fuck you managed to move them...
他们现在他妈的在哪里
and where the fuck they are now.
副局长
Deputy...
我不知这该从何说起 不过我们
I don't know quite how to put this, but we...
我是说 我
I mean, I...
我开始区分我辖区内的地段
I began by identifying those areas of my district...
在哪里的毒品交易破坏最小
where drug trafficking was least harmful.
我试图把所有的街头交易 驱赶到那些地段
I proceeded to push all street-level dealing towards those areas.
刚开始时
Now, at first...
跟街角的少年毒贩打交道 我没什么成效
dealing with the juveniles on them corners, I had little success.
不过最终
But ultimately...
靠招集我辖区内所有的中层毒贩
by rounding up all the mid-level dealers in my district...
给他们一个他们无法拒绝的提议
and making them an offer they couldn't refuse...
- 我能够让 - 你给他们一个提议吗
- I was able to... - You made them an offer?
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
除非他们把他们的人马
Either they move their people
迁到三个指定区域之一
to one of three designated areas...
在那里 缉毒不是警察优先任务
where drug enforcement was not a district priority...
否则他们要面对我辖区每个警察的打击
or they face the wrath of every able-bodied soul in my district.
局长 我不明白啊
Major, I don't understand.
我们唯一能控制毒品街角的时候 就是我们指派警官在那里站岗
The only time we can hold a drug corner is when we assign officers to stand there.
你的幻灯片显示 任何街角没有安排任何警力
Your slides don't suggest any concerted deployment on any corners.
你怎么能够...
How were you able to...
老天啊 你个笨笨 你看不出他做了什么吗
Jesus Christ, you nit, don't you see what he's done?
他把毒品合法化了
He's legalized drugs!
实际上 我选择无视他们
Actually, I elected to ignore them.
你他妈的发疯了 他他妈的发疯了
You lost your fucking mind. He's lost his fucking mind.
你 到我办公室 马上
You, in my office. Now!
好吧
Okay.
就这样 先生们
That's it, gentlemen.
她出发了
She's a go.
开演了 Bubs
Showtime, Bubs.
靠
Oh, shit.
- Squeak妹妹 - 老底哥Bubbles
- Sister Squeak. - Bottom-end Bubbles.
你去哪儿了 妞儿 好长时间啦
Where you been, girl? Been a long time.
T恤衫
T-shirts?
T恤衫有啥赚头儿
What the hell kind of money is in T-shirts?
妞儿 你还不知道
Girl, you just don't know.
你情况怎样 我听说你被关起来了
But how's your game? I heard you was locked up.
靠 我上报纸有一年啦 我还有事要办
Shit, I been on paper for a year. I got some things going.
- 对啊 我瞧出来了 气色这么好 - 他怎么样
- Yeah, I can see that. Looking all good... - How's he doing?
在把猫从鱼筐里劝出来
Talk a cat off a fish cart.
好吧 Bubs 我得走啦
All right, Bubs, I gotta get.
咱们回头见
I'll see you later on.
喂Squeak 我差点忘了
Yo, Squeak, Squeak! I about forgot.
你如果用得着  我可以把这个很便宜卖给你
I can sell you one of these real cheap, if you got use for the shit.
我死翘翘了
I'm fucking dead.
你是说 咱们要死翘翘了 咱们都要栽在这上面
You mean, we're fucking dead. We're all dead behind this shit.
老天爷啊
Jesus Christ.
你们瞧 我做的事 是刻意为之 自作主张
You know, what I did, I did knowingly and on my own.
我是说 我的下属与此无关
I mean, my men had nothing to do with this.
他们以为 这是某种精心圈套的一部分
They thought it was part of some elaborate trap.
如果你需要我来背黑锅 我可以接受
So if you need me to fall on that sword, I'm good with that.
你可以接受
You're good with it?
你知道我有休假时间
Hey, you know I got my vacation time,
另外 一两个月后 我就执勤30年了
and that's 30 in a couple of months.
如果你要我来扛 我都准备好了
So if you need me to fall, I'm ready.
不过 别告诉我 你要对我的下属采取任何惩罚措施
But don't let me hear that you're taking any punitive action against my people.
因为我会大肆宣传 我还可以跟下一任一样说谎
Because I can get on the soapbox, and I can lie as good as the next man...
如果我迫不得已
if I have to.
你在威胁我吗
Are you threatening me?
我想是的 长官
I believe I am, sir.
我很抱歉
My apologies.
Bunny 你个混蛋 我得夸你这个 绝妙好计
Bunny, you cocksucker, I gotta give it to you! A brilliant idea!
疯狂且非法 不过无论如何 绝对妙不可言
Insane and illegal, but stone-fucking brilliant, nonetheless.
在我强压众人降低犯罪数据之后
After all my putting my foot up people's asses to decrease the numbers,
他来了 一招制敌
he comes in and in one stroke...
降低了他妈的14%
gets a fucking 14% decrease.
这要终结了我们的前途 太他妈的可惜了 不过还是很赞啊
Fucking shame it's gonna end our careers, but still...
你们可能听够了我的话 不过
Look, y'all probably tired of hearing from me, but...
我带来这些来信
I brought these letters...
来自社区组织 部门官员 商业人士 普通市民
from community associations, ministers, business people, citizens.
它们都是正面评价
And they're all positive.
毒贩离开街角 他们都很高兴
They're all happy that the dealers are off the corners.
你以为 这能挽救我们吗
You think that's gonna save our asses,
是吗
do you?
不 我看不行 不过
No, I guess not, but
这些和我的警徽 是我拥有的一切
that and my badge is all I got.
我要收了你的警徽 局长
I might have your badge, Major,
可是不是今天
but not today.
在我们准备好声明以前
I don't wanna draw any attention to this shit...
我不想把任何注意引到这摊屎上
before we're ready to speak to it.
如果你有任何休假时间
So if you have any vacation time,
你现在就用吧
you're taking it now.
在通知以前
Do not report for a shift
别来上班
until notified.
还有件事 长官
One more thing, sir.
一个太阳报记者发现了我的安排
A Sun reporter is aware of my deployment.
我告诉他 一次调查悬而未决
I told him an investigation was pending.
他拖延拖延这次报道
He promised to delay the article.
多长时间
How long?
大概一周 最多
About a week, tops.
早年间 我跟Superstroke帮 搞合作生意
I was with Superstroke on the pool circuit in the early days...
大部分是扒窃和小骗局
the mostly it was pickpocketing and short cons.
在手机流行以前  我窃取过长途电话卡话费
I did the long-distance access card heist before cell phones got popular.
你能破解号码吗
You crypt numbers?
行 我喜欢在机场地区
Yeah, I favored the airports, yeah.
- 你还能听出号码吗 - 喔 喔 这是咋回事
- Can you still read numbers? - Whoa, whoa, what's up with this?
你男人以为我带来烂卖家吗
Your man think I brought him bad merchandise?
如果他这么认为 我们可以马上走人
'Cause if that what he think, we can just beat feet right now.
靠 Bernard  你为啥来这套间谍把戏
Damn, Bernard, why you acting all CIA and shit?
咱们是来赚钱的
We trying to make money here.
如果你必须向我要汇报的人解释
If you had to answer to the people I do...
你他妈的会更小心的 告诉你吧
your ass would be damn more sight cautious, too, that's all I'm saying.
我欣赏谨慎从事
I appreciate caution,
因为我在这儿也有风险
'cause I'm hanging out here, too.
试试吧 用手机来
Give it a go. Use a cell phone.
Marlene 你把那复印件发到巴黎了吗
Marlene, you send that copy off to Paris?
谢谢 宝贝儿
Thank you, darling.
那样可以 我在机场
That will work. I'm at the airport.
穿梭巴士 对
The shuttle, yes.
3-1-0-4-4-8-
16-91-
7-7-8-3-1-2
最后一个数字可能是7
Now, that last number might be a seven.
对这些小键盘手机 我不太有把握
I'm not too sure with these small keypads and all.
咱们可以做生意
We can do business.
就这样 1 2 1 2 1 2
That's it. One-two, one-two, one-two.
1 2 就这样 1 2 你继续
One-two, that's it. One-two, there you go.
好吧 就这样 现在你懂了
All right, there it is. Now you getting it.
把左手抬起来
Keep that left hand up.
好的 现在注意你的平衡
All right. Watch your balance now.
不要前倾 别太前倾 别太前倾 好吗
Don't lean forward. Don't lean too much. Don't lean too forward, all right?
好的 来吧 别太前倾 很好
All right, let's go. Don't lean too forward, that's right.
1 2 转身
One-two, pivot.
你在开玩笑
You're kidding.
告诉我 他在开玩笑
Tell me he's kidding.
你在开玩笑 对吧
You're kidding, right?
他瞒着我操作的
He did it without our knowledge.
瞒着你
Without your knowledge.
那更糟糕 你是总局长
Well, that's worse. You're the Commissioner.
以前是局长
Was the Commissioner.
你以为这篓子能在这里解决 你搞错了
You think the buck's gonna stop in this office, you're wrong.
请容许我
If I might...
这些是他辖区的来信
these are letters from people in his district.
部门官员 生意人 选民
Ministers, business people, voters.
全是溢美之辞
All glowing reports.
另外 西区有14%的犯罪下降
And there's the 14% reductionin crime in the Western.
这可不是寻常事
That's not an anomaly.
这是硬指标
It's hard data.
眼下 咱们可以把它收拾干净 把它抹掉
Now, we can clean it up, make it go away.
媒体可能已经收到风声 不过我们可以把这
The press might already have wind of it, but we can explain
解释成一种新策略
that as some sort of a new initiative.
来诱捕毒贩高层
Trap high-end drug dealers.
14%
14%.
如果我们处理得当
If we handle this right,
我们也许都能逃过一劫
we might all get out from underneath.
谁都没污点
No mud on anybody.
不 不行
No. No.
我信任过你 Erv 我非常信任
I trusted you, Erv, I really did.
你让我失望
You let me down.
这事搞砸 损失就大发了
Now, this thing goes wrong, no telling the damage.
处理不好 你得走人
On this, you walk point.
那就是解决之道 Erv 你跟我一样明白
That's the way things work, Erv. You know it as well as I do.
谢谢 Ervin
Thank you, Ervin.
我很快会有怎样立即处理
I'll be over shortly is the detailed plan on
这个烂摊子的详细安排
how this shit gets cleaned up immediately.
如果你能给这玩意儿换个名称
If you could call this shit something other than what it is...
压根别想
Don't even think it.
折扣传呼机和电子产品
事情是这么安排的
The way it works is this.
如果超期60天 你还没给你的手机充值
If you don't re-up the minutes on your cell phone before 60 days...
移动公司就回收那些号码
the wireless company recycles the phone numbers.
我就在那里搞到号码
And that's where I get them.
我放出风声说  我要收购一次性手机
I put the word out on the street that I'm buying tossed-off burners...
每个两美元
paying $2 a pop.
街上的人拿成百个给我
Street people bring me hundreds.
我把它们拿到我侄女这里 她在电脑上设置一下
I bring them in here to my niece, she jiggles the computer...
用假帐号给每台充值200分钟
juices them up another 200 minutes on a bogus account.
那样给手机自动延长
And that automatically extends the life of the phone
使用期60天
for another 60 days.
她这里每台收我20美元
She charges me $20 on each phone on her end.
我翻倍加价后卖到街上 获得我的利润
I double it or more on the street to make mine.
你说的是什么意思
So what you saying?
宝贝儿 正常预付费手机 有200 或者400分钟通话时间
Baby, a standard Tracfone with 200, maybe 400 minutes
每台至少要花你150美元 200美元
on it gonna run you $150, $200 easy.
即使我每台要你100美元 你每台至少赚50美元
I charge you an even $100. You clear $50 on each phone.
如果你能给它们 提供相应的收据 那才可以
That's if you can back them up with receipts.
我必须给他们明显来自 不同卖点的收据 否则我不干
I gotta show receipts looking like they from different places, or I can't play.
咱们能配合这位先生吗
Can we accommodate the good man?
靠 Calvin  你明知我今晚要玩游戏的
Damn, Calvin, you know I got the bingo tonight.
听着 朋友 我不确定你想来这里与否
Look, friend, I ain't sure you wanna be around here...
我能肯定我们受够你了
and I'm damn sure we're getting tired of having you.
够明白了吧
That plain enough?
你现在该明白  我不想混迹于同性恋场所
You should know by now, I don't wanna be around no bunch of cocksucking faggots.
可是在我遇到Omar以前 我会不停到访的
But I ain't gonna stop coming round till I run up on Omar.
你该把话传出去
You might want to get the word out.
最后说一次 我不认识他
For the last time, I don't know him.
那我明天再来
Then I'm back tomorrow.
也许我能帮到你
Maybe I can help you?
我从未怀疑过
I don't doubt it for a minute.